http://www.saintmarthas.org/privacy-policy/

Contact Us:
P.O. Box 4950, St. Louis, MO 63108
314-533-1313 (available 24/7)
Monetary Donations Only:
St. Martha's HallMailstop 472001, P.O. Box 953745St. Louis, MO 63195-3745
News & Events
Welcome We are here to help abused women and their children break the cycle of violence in their lives by offering safe, confidential shelter and services.
Subscribe to our mailing list
* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
*
Last Name
*
Please Note Some communication over the Internet is NOT confidential and can be traced. Please call us if this is a concern. Additionally, if you are concerned for your safety, click here to learn how to clear website history from popular Internet browsers.
NavigationHome
About Us
Services
Resources
Ways To Help
History
Are You A Feminist
Children’s Program
News & Events
St. Martha’s Hall Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information on or through this site that can personally identify you only when it is voluntarily offered by you. For example, we collect personally identifiable information to thank our donors.
We do not share any of the personal information you provide to us with any third party.
Like many other organizations, we may use “cookie” technology, where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor’s computer. This information helps us determine in the aggregate the total number of visitors to the site on an ongoing basis and the types of Internet browsers and operating systems used by our visitors. This information is used to enhance your on-line visits. Under no circumstances do we use this information to personally identify visitors or cross-reference the information with any type of personal information that is voluntarily offered on or through the site.
The safety and security of your credit card transactions are important to us. We utilize PayPal for financial donations. You get an extra layer of security when you use PayPal. That’s because all your financial information (like your credit card number) is securely stored and encrypted on PayPal’s servers, so you don’t need to share your financial information with us. We do not have control over or responsibility for the data collection and use practices of third parties that process online donation credit card transactions.
We do not rent, sell, loan, trade or lease the addresses on our postal or electronic mailing lists to anyone. St. Martha’s Hall may modify this policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on this site. Unless we specifically provide otherwise, this policy only applies to this site and our online activities, and does not apply to any of our offline activities.
© Copyright 2020 St. Martha's Hall. All Rights Reserved.     |     990/Annual Report     |     Privacy Policy
7ads6x98y
